[
  {
    "question": "Nancy Holt collaborated with Robert Smithson to make the tongue-in-cheek film",
    "a": "Boomerang",
    "b": "Pine Barrens",
    "c": "Revolve",
    "d": "Underscan",
    "e": "East Coast/West Coast",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "In college, Nancy Holt studied",
    "a": "biology",
    "b": "English",
    "c": "ecology",
    "d": "psychology",
    "e": "visual arts",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sun Tunnels lies in",
    "a": "California’s Mojave Desert",
    "b": "Utah’s Great Basin Desert",
    "c": "Nevada’s Death Valley",
    "d": "Arizona’s Sonoran Desert",
    "e": "New Mexico’s Chihuahuan Desert",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "The diagonal of Sun Tunnels measures closest to",
    "a": "75 feet",
    "b": "95 feet",
    "c": "115 feet",
    "d": "85 feet",
    "e": "105 feet",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which of the following journals did Nancy Holt publish her essay on Sun Tunnels?",
    "a": "Aesthetica",
    "b": "Artforum",
    "c": "Apollo",
    "d": "ArtNexus",
    "e": "Art Bulletin",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following constellations is NOT represented in Sun Tunnels?",
    "a": "Orion",
    "b": "Draco",
    "c": "Columba",
    "d": "Capricorn",
    "e": "Perseus",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Robert Smithson died while working on an artwork called",
    "a": "Asphalt Rundown",
    "b": "Broken Circle/Spiral Hill",
    "c": "Glue Pour",
    "d": "Spiral Jetty",
    "e": "Amarillo Ramp",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following Nancy Holt films honors her late husband Robert Smithson?",
    "a": "East Coast/West Coast",
    "b": "Underscan",
    "c": "Pine Barrens",
    "d": "Boomerang",
    "e": "Revolve",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the early 2010s, Sun Tunnels acquired",
    "a": "large red spots",
    "b": "additional supports",
    "c": "small, circular markings",
    "d": "widespread cracks",
    "e": "additional constellations",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "With which of the following statements would Nancy Holt MOST agree?",
    "a": "Art installations should be temporary to avoid long-term environmental impact.",
    "b": "Earthworks should not make significant changes to their landscapes.",
    "c": "Artworks should be preserved in their exact original state.",
    "d": "Art should dominate its environment to make a bold statement.",
    "e": "Earthworks should be left to change alongside their surroundings.",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "The site of Dark Star Park once housed a(n)",
    "a": "factory and mining operation",
    "b": "gas station and warehouse",
    "c": "farm and grain silo",
    "d": "abandoned mall and office building",
    "e": "landfill and parking lot",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Dark Star Park connect to its environment?",
    "a": "It has shadow markers that temporarily align with actual shadows.",
    "b": "It uses plants and vegetation native to the surrounding area.",
    "c": "The central ball aligns with the summer solstice's setting sun.",
    "d": "It incorporates recycled materials from nearby locations.",
    "e": "When viewed from above the balls match the constellation Leo.",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why was August 1 significant to Nancy Holt when making Dark Star Park?",
    "a": "It was Robert Smithson’s birthday.",
    "b": "It marked the anniversary of the park’s opening.",
    "c": "It was the date Rosslyn was founded.",
    "d": "It was the date of a solar eclipse.",
    "e": "It was the date of a major local festival.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "A viewer watching the interviews in The Making of Dark Star Park learns MOST about",
    "a": "its astronomical significance",
    "b": "its emphasis on collaboration",
    "c": "its environmental themes",
    "d": "Robert Smithson’s contributions",
    "e": "Rosslyn’s history",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sun Tunnels and Dark Star Park are connected to all of the following elements EXCEPT",
    "a": "time cycles",
    "b": "conservationism",
    "c": "local businesses",
    "d": "the land art movement",
    "e": "celestial bodies",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which state was Mark Dion born?",
    "a": "Pennsylvania",
    "b": "West Virginia",
    "c": "Massachusetts",
    "d": "New York",
    "e": "Maryland",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Mark Dion complete his independent study program?",
    "a": "Museum of Fine Arts Boston",
    "b": "The Metropolitan Museum of Art",
    "c": "The Art Institute of Chicago",
    "d": "The Whitney Museum of American Art",
    "e": "The Guggenheim Museum",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of tree did Neukom Vivarium use?",
    "a": "olive",
    "b": "hemlock",
    "c": "elm",
    "d": "willow",
    "e": "beech",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "With which artist did Mark Dion collaborate to create Mildred’s Lane?",
    "a": "J. Morgan Puett",
    "b": "Hans Haacke",
    "c": "Jack Burnham",
    "d": "William Beebe",
    "e": "Nancy Holt",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Mark Dion spend days cataloging in the performance component of A Meter of Jungle?",
    "a": "invertebrates",
    "b": "sediment",
    "c": "leaves",
    "d": "flowers",
    "e": "reptiles",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What component of A Meter of Jungle still exists today?",
    "a": "a recording of the excavation",
    "b": "a selection of the categorized samples",
    "c": "a photograph of the land plot",
    "d": "a photograph of the sculpture",
    "e": "a video of the performance",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city did A Meter of Jungle debut?",
    "a": "Lima",
    "b": "Mexico City",
    "c": "São Paulo",
    "d": "Valencia",
    "e": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Mark Dion acquire the material for The N.Y. Bureau of Tropical Conservation?",
    "a": "Brazil",
    "b": "Argentina",
    "c": "Venezuela",
    "d": "Colombia",
    "e": "Peru",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which field of science is MOST related to A Meter of Jungle?",
    "a": "Pathology",
    "b": "Phytology",
    "c": "Anthropology",
    "d": "Entomology",
    "e": "Geology",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artwork did Mark Dion create FIRST?",
    "a": "On Tropical Nature",
    "b": "Tropical Rainforest Preserves",
    "c": "The N.Y. Bureau of Tropical Conservation",
    "d": "Neukom Vivarium",
    "e": "A Meter of Jungle",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sculptures did Mark Dion construct using the samples gathered as a part of On Tropical Nature?",
    "a": "six",
    "b": "one",
    "c": "eight",
    "d": "three",
    "e": "four",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Criticisms of Mark Dion’s work often described it as being",
    "a": "without message",
    "b": "lazy",
    "c": "inexact",
    "d": "overly meticulous",
    "e": "antiquated",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ecological crisis MOST directly threatened Antarctica in the 1980s?",
    "a": "urbanization",
    "b": "acid rain",
    "c": "waste disposal",
    "d": "nuclear energy",
    "e": "the ozone hole",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which group hosted the “Earth Summit” of 1992 in Rio de Janeiro?",
    "a": "The World Wildlife Fund",
    "b": "The World Health Organization",
    "c": "The Environmental Protection Agency",
    "d": "The International Atomic Energy Commission",
    "e": "The United Nations",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "In artist statements and interviews, Mark Dion connects his environmental work to the social issue of",
    "a": "poverty",
    "b": "racism",
    "c": "colonialism",
    "d": "sexism",
    "e": "war",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  }
]